I mean, it's just an incredible, like, that is the question we've been up, what is this about?
It's just an extraordinary, I mean, stream of consciousness.
Though he's obviously thought about it quite a lot.
I think it's a PB for Keezy, Dave, to have two people just staring at it in blankly going,
what are you talking about?
Not that it was completely outlandish.
I mean, he, you know, he backed it all up.
It was a good, I mean, it wasn't a completely outlandish name.
It wasn't Roberto Martinez or anything like that.
that but i think my name wasn't the kind of structure that to go with it was but it was
quite yeah it's quite a progressive uh view from for kesey xabi alonso is the sort of name you'd
expect the uh the stats nerds to be to be pushing for these sorts of jobs kesey normally would go
go with what he knows the five years thing you're telling me that if if xabi alonso gets this job
got this job somehow in the summer or whatever and it was all going to shit come next december you
wouldn't be you wouldn't be saying it wouldn't be in his blog yeah he wouldn't be saying don't
worry jabi jabi a loser get him out of that club before we tear apart some of these details you
have to remember the context in which it's being delivered i think at first gray sort of gives him
carte blanche and says right you're in charge of man united what would you do and then kesey ignores
that and basically starts talking like a management consultant who's been drafted in to tell man united
what to do exactly like i think he would actually say if he was i think my favorite bit dave is where
he's assessing alonso's impact oliverkusen says that everything he's done has what hasn't turned
to gold but that's amazing that's so good that's the sprinkling of partridge that you need i think
yeah it's just that just the checking of himself and styling it out i just think it's just utterly
superb yeah and then on top of that the the slight irritation when anyone challenges him on anything
like mackett's saying he wouldn't he wouldn't go there why not why wouldn't he go there because
one minute he's saying the top players just not gonna go they're just not gonna go there yeah and
then he says that this guy who's who's been fated as the you know the the as he says the next best
young thing not even the next big thing the next best young thing would go there there are two things
amazing as well with that uh not quite gold is that gray really earnestly responds to that as well
no no no like as if that is like they are really gonna get into what he's turned it to the other
thing i'm that i am just really curious about like dave says xavi alonso is a is a weird one for keys to
come out with so i'm just really fascinated as to what is it about alonso that is it that he likes
alonso's look and that he thinks you know he's you know he he's got something about him well this is it
i mean as we all know from sort of the body of his work on being sports from the last year or so the
one thing he values over anything else at the management is someone who's got a big character
a big personality yeah and that's what i think he alonso has he has that kind of statesman like
kind of sort of stature about him already won everything played for big clubs yeah yeah i suppose
so he's got that gravitas at the big moments at big clubs on big nights and i think he's ready for
the big job and there we are saudi money where's that coming from by the way hilarious absolutely
brilliant what a return to form for being sports generally and brilliant stuff thanks to you charlie
eccleshare thank you thanks to you dave walker thank you thanks to everyone for listening we'll be back
on thursday see ya
this podcast is part of the sports social podcast network
for the ones who get it done the most important part is the one you need now and the best partner
is the one who can deliver that's why millions of maintenance and repair pros trust granger because
we have professional grade supplies for every industry even hard to find products and we have
same day pickup and next day delivery on most orders but most importantly we have an unwavering commitment
to help keep you up and running call click granger.com or just stop by granger for the ones who get it done