I'm sorry, you can sit there and look and play with all your silly machines as much as you like.
Is Gascoigne going to have a crack? He is, you know.
Oh, he's there!
Brilliant!
The change!
He's ran the goalkeeper, he's done it!
Absolutely incredible!
He launched himself six feet into the crowd, and Kung Fu kicked a supporter who was eye-whip
without a shadow of a doubt giving him lip.
Oh, I say! It's amazing!
He does it time, and time, and time again.
Crank up the music! Charge a glass!
This nation is going to dance all night!
A lovely brace of shot urging from the travelling Watford faithful.
Troy Deeney's cruel dig at a Sunday evening TV stalwart.
Seamus Coleman produces the most loyal 3.67 seconds in football history.